Toothpaste is making you dumber. Let me explain.
The majority of all toothpaste have a toxic chemical in them that destroys an important
gland in your brain. This substance is known as fluoride. The government wants you to think
that fluoride is good for you and that it's safe, but that's just a lie. Fluoride calcifies
an important gland in your brain known as the pineal gland. This gland is responsible for many things
like your circadian cycle and hormone secretion. Many also believe that the pineal gland is the
seed of the soul and is where you unlock higher consciousness. Side effects of having a calcified
pineal gland include a wide range of neuronal diseases like Alzheimer's and also disruption
of melatonin and serotonin levels. To combat this, you have two options. Find a trusted brand
of fluoride-free toothpaste or make your own toothpaste by mixing coconut oil, baking soda,
sea salt and essential oils like mint. If they can't get you with toothpaste, they'll try and
get you with the tap water. There's a reason fluoride is banned in many European countries.
The United States has one of the most corrupt systems in the world all to keep you sick and dumb.
Luckily, there are people trying to expose this corruption like me. It's up to you to decide what
you want to believe, the lies or the real truth. Follow Divine Herbal Roots for more daily tips
about real health.